auntyflo.com 2019-07-27

# Privacy Policy | Auntyflo.com

Thank you so much for visiting our website.

Your privacy and the security of your personal information are very important to us. We want you to be as comfortable as possible visiting our website and using our internet services.

We are dedicated to protecting the privacy of those who visit our website and use our services. This Privacy Policy governs the United Kingdom and Ireland websites operated by us (our "website") and our internet services and explains how we collect your personal information on our website or through our internet services, how we protect such information, and the choices you have concerning the use of such information. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. We will not sell, share, licence, trade, or rent your personal information collected on our Website or through the internet services to others. Please note: We do not send random marketing emails to personal email addresses (spam).

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will post any changes to this Privacy Policy here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and whether we will disclose that information to anyone. Please refer back to this Privacy Policy on a regular basis. By using our Website or any of our products, offerings, features, tools or resources that we provide on our Website (collectively, our "Internet services"), you agree to the terms of this

Privacy Policy.

Please remember that this Privacy Policy applies only to information collected by our Website. We are not responsible for the privacy of any information you reveal or post in any public forum (e.g., message board) or for the privacy practices of websites that are operated or owned by third parties.

We may collect information (including information that is Personally Identifiable Information) from you in different manners and at different places and times on our website, such as when you become a community user on our website or subscribe to one of our internet services. We may also collect information from you in connection with, or through, other Internet services we may make available on our Website from time to time. The following is a description of the areas and/or manners in which we primarily collect information about you.

In order to access certain Internet services on our website, such as our forums must first complete certain steps to become registered. During these steps, you may be required to provide us with information (including Personally Identifiable Information) such as name, postcode and email address, and, if you subscribe to one of our Internet services, credit card and billing information. This information is used to help us understand who uses our Website, to improve our Website and our internet services, to contact users about requested internet services and/or for subscription billing purposes. Providing this information is encouraged so we can provide a more personalised experience on our Website.

Cookies and Action Tags.

We do not collect Personally Identifiable Information passively using "cookies" and "action tags."

**Referral Programmes.**

Through third party referral programme operators and others, we offer referral programmes whereby referral websites can earn commissions through the referral of subscribers or other purchasers to our Website. To track the earning of such commissions, and to determine the effectiveness of the referral programmes, purchasers through such referral websites are tracked using technologies that do not include Personally Identifiable Information (such as cookies and/or action tags). Our programme operators and the referral websites themselves can only access non-personally Identifiable Information such as data relating to the number of impressions served, the number of transactions completed, and their resulting earnings. They cannot access our customers' personal data.

If you choose to apply to a referral website, we use the data you provide strictly for conducting business with you. We have entered into certain agreements with third party program operators for the purpose of administering our referral programmes. Should you become a referral website of ours through one of our third party programme operators, any information you provide to them is subject to their privacy policies.

**Internet Services.**

We collect information, some of which may be Personally Identifiable Information, that you voluntarily provide to us when you choose to use some of our Internet Services. We collect this information in order to personalise your Internet experience. If you wish for us not to collect this data please [contact us](https://www.auntyflo.com/contact)

**Newsletter**

We collect information, some of which it may be Personally Identifiable Information that you voluntarily provide to us when you choose to sign up for our services. We collect this information in order to personalise your Internet experience. If you wish for us not to collect this data please [contact us.](https://www.auntyflo.com/contact)

**Public Forums and the Public Profile Feature.**

THIS PRIVACY POLICY DOES NOT PROTECT YOU WHEN YOU USE OUR PUBLIC FORUMS OR PROVIDE INFORMATION (INCLUDING PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION) ABOUT YOURSELF THROUGH THE PUBLIC PROFILE FEATURE AVAILABLE ON OUR WEBSITE. You should be aware that information shared in a public forum may be seen or collected by third parties that do not adhere to our Privacy Policy. You should think carefully before disclosing any information in any public forum, or through the Public Profile feature, on our Website.

**Log Files**

We also collect Non-Personally Identifiable Information through our Internet log files, which record data such as user IP addresses, browser types, domain names, and other anonymous statistical data involving the use of our Website. This information may be used to analyse trends, to administer the Website, to monitor our Website's use, and to gather general demographic information.

**Email a Friend or a Parent**

Through our Email a Friend or Email a Parent tool on our Website, we will automatically send your friend a one-time email containing the information you request to be sent. If you elect to use the Email a Friend or Parent tool, we will collect from you Personally Identifiable Information about your friend or Parent which you have provided, such as your friend's or Parent's name and email address. We recommend, however, that you make sure that your friend or parent wants to receive emails from you regarding materials on our Website.

**Third Parties Generally.**

We may provide to third parties information about you that does not allow you to be identified or contacted, including where such information is combined with similar information of other users of our Website. For example, we might inform third parties regarding the number of unique users who visit our website, the demographic breakdown of our users of our website, or the activities that visitors to our website engage in while on our website. The third parties to which we may provide this information may include potential or actual advertisers, providers of advertising services (including website tracking services), commercial partners, sponsors, licensees, researchers and other similar parties. We do not trade or sell email addresses or personal contact information.

**Outside Contractors.**

We may employ independent contractors, vendors and suppliers (collectively, "Outside Contractors") to provide specific services and products related to our website or Internet services , such as hosting, website design, maintaining our forums, providing credit card processing and fraud screening, and developing applications for our website and e-mail services.

These Outside Contractors may sometimes have limited access to information collected on our website, including your Personally Identifiable Information, in the course of providing products or services to us. Access to your Personally Identifiable Information by these contractors is limited to the information reasonably necessary in order for the Outside Contractors to perform their limited function for us.

**We also require that these contractors to:**

(i) protect the privacy of your Personally Identifiable Information consistent with this Privacy Policy, and (ii) not use or disclose your Personally Identifiable Information for any purpose other than providing us with products or services for which we contracted.

**Third Party Sellers.**

In addition, through our Website, you may be given the opportunity to purchase (or to obtain more information regarding) certain content, products or services which are sold through a person or company other than us (collectively, "Third Party Sellers"). We will attempt to make it clear to you when you are dealing with a Third Party Seller by opening a new browser or otherwise notifying you that you are leaving our Website. For example, if you see a phrase such as "powered by" or "brought to you by" followed by the name of a person or company other than Get Into Uni, then you are likely on, or about to enter, a website hosted or operated by a person or company other than us. Third Party Sellers may request that you submit certain information to them in order to purchase their products or services or to obtain additional information from them. You do not need to submit this information or purchase any products or services from Third Party Sellers to access our Website. By submitting the requested information, you affirmatively consent to have that information shared with the Third Party Seller. This information is used by the Third Party Seller and may be subject to a different privacy policy.

**Sale of Business.**

We reserve the right to transfer information (including your Personally Identifiable Information) to a third party in the event of a sale, merger or other transfer of all or substantially all of the assets of any of us or our Affiliates provided that the third party agrees to adhere to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

BY USING OUR WEBSITE, YOU SIGNIFY YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND OF US PROCESSING YOUR PERSONAL DATA IN ACCORDANCE WITH THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY, YOU SHOULD NOT USE OUR WEBSITE. YOU’RE CONTINUED USE OF OUR WEBSITE FOLLOWING THE POSTING OF CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY WILL MEAN THAT YOU ACCEPT THOSE CHANGES.
